Kolya Harutyunyan

Frontend Developer

Respected Frontend Developer with more than 5 years of experience in collaborating with creative and development teams on the execution of ideas and projects. *Key skills include:* ● Promoting and communicating new ideas ● Creating process improvements ● Instituting new technologies ● Writing maintainable cross-browser code ● Estimating time and costs for projects ● Ensuring code is scalable and responsive



- haryan.geko@gmail.com
- Yerevan, Armenia
- in linkedin.com/in/kolya-harutyunyan-3a11a320b
- S live:.cid.80f67e47f57f1f6f

- +37498741604
- kolyaharutyunyan.github.io/my-portfolio/
- witter.com/Kolya80264360
- github.com/KolyaHarutyunyan

WORK EXPERIENCE

Middle Frontend Developer Marpla

03/2023 - Present Tyumen, Russia

Providing SEO optimization for the WildBerries Sellers and many more

Software Engineer Solicy

12/2022 - 02/2023

Yerevan, Armenia

Solicy is a fast-growing company providing Blockchain and Software solutions to customers all over the world.

Frontend Web Developer ITHire

05/2018 - 11/2021 Freelance Company Yerevan, Armenia

Achievements/Tasks

- Translate designs to front-end code, estimate project time and costs, determine developer requirements and specifications, and work with cross-functional team to define and develop product roadmaps.
- Notable accomplishment:

 Increased scalability,
 maintainability, and responsiveness of cross-browser code.

Frontend Web Developer EACHBASE

11/2021 - 11/2022

Yerevan, Armenia

EACHBASE is a digital agency founded in 2018 and based in Los Angeles, CA, USA.

Achievements/Tasks

- Updated and streamlined existing code to improve site performance for entire company. Notable Accomplishments:
 - Utilized cutting-edge JavaScript and HTML 5 techniques, frameworks, and libraries. Wrote support documentation and provided training to internal and external users.

SKILLS



LANGUAGES

Armenian

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Professional Working Proficiency

Russian

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS



EDUCATION

Faculty of Regulation of Economy and International Economic Relations
ASUE (Armenian State University of Economics)

09/2015 - 05/2020

Yerevan, Armenia